<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My SDG App</string>

    <string name="sdg_name">SDG</string>
    <string name="sdg_desc">What does it bring?</string>
    <string name="btn_more">See more</string>
    <string name="list">List</string>
    <string name="grid">Grid</string>

    <string-array name="data_sdg_name">
        <item>No Poverty</item>
        <item>Zero Hunger</item>
        <item>Good Health and Well-Being</item>
        <item>Quality Education</item>
        <item>Gender Equality</item>
        <item>Clean Water and Sanitation</item>
        <item>Affordable and Clean Energy</item>
        <item>Decent Work and Economic Growth</item>
        <item>Industry, Innovation, and Infrastructure</item>
        <item>Reduced Inequalities</item>
        <item>Sustainable Cities and Communities</item>
        <item>Responsible Consumption and Production</item>
        <item>Climate Action</item>
        <item>Life Below Water</item>
        <item>Life on Island</item>
        <item>Peace, Justice, and Strong Institutions</item>
        <item>Partnerships for the Goals</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_sdg_desc">
        <item>End poverty in all its forms everywhere.</item>
        <item>End hunger, achieve food security and improved nutrition and promote sustainable agriculture.</item>
        <item>Ensure healthy lives and promote well-being for all at all ages.</item>
        <item>Ensure inclusive and equitable quality education and promote lifelong learning opportunities for all.</item>
        <item>Achieve gender equality and empower all women and girls.</item>
        <item>Ensure availability and sustainable management of water and sanitation for all.</item>
        <item>Ensure access to affordable, reliable, sustainable and modern energy for all.</item>
        <item>Promote sustained, inclusive and sustainable economic growth, full and productive employment and decent work for all.</item>
        <item>Build resilient infrastructure, promote inclusive and sustainable industrialization and foster innovation.</item>
        <item>Reduce inequality within and among countries.</item>
        <item>Make cities and human settlements inclusive, safe, resilient and sustainable.</item>
        <item>Ensure sustainable consumption and production patterns.</item>
        <item>Take urgent action to combat climate change and its impacts.</item>
        <item>Conserve and sustainably use the oceans, seas and marine resources for sustainable development.</item>
        <item>Protect, restore and promote sustainable use of terrestrial ecosystems, sustainably manage forests, combat desertification, and halt and reverse land degradation and halt biodiversity loss.</item>
        <item>Promote peaceful and inclusive societies for sustainable development, provide access to justice for all and build effective, accountable and inclusive institutions at all levels.</item>
        <item>Strengthen the means of implementation and revitalize the Global Partnership for Sustainable Development.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_sdg_content">
        <item>The first Sustainable Development Goal aims to “End poverty in all its forms everywhere”. Its seven associated targets aims, among others, to eradicate extreme poverty for all people everywhere, reduce at least by half the proportion of men, women and children of all ages living in poverty, and implement nationally appropriate social protection systems and measures for all, including floors, and by 2030 achieve substantial coverage of the poor and the vulnerable</item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name= "data_photo">
        <item>https://archium.ateneo.edu/un-sdg-icons/1000/thumbnail.jpg</item>
        <item>https://archium.ateneo.edu/un-sdg-icons/1001/thumbnail.jpg</item>
        <item>https://archium.ateneo.edu/un-sdg-icons/1002/thumbnail.jpg</item>
        <item>https://archium.ateneo.edu/un-sdg-icons/1003/thumbnail.jpg</item>
        <item>https://archium.ateneo.edu/un-sdg-icons/1004/thumbnail.jpg</item>
        <item>https://archium.ateneo.edu/un-sdg-icons/1005/thumbnail.jpg</item>
        <item>https://archium.ateneo.edu/un-sdg-icons/1006/thumbnail.jpg</item>
        <item>https://archium.ateneo.edu/un-sdg-icons/1007/thumbnail.jpg</item>
        <item>https://archium.ateneo.edu/un-sdg-icons/1008/thumbnail.jpg</item>
        <item>https://archium.ateneo.edu/un-sdg-icons/1009/thumbnail.jpg</item>
        <item>https://archium.ateneo.edu/un-sdg-icons/1010/thumbnail.jpg</item>
        <item>https://archium.ateneo.edu/un-sdg-icons/1011/thumbnail.jpg</item>
        <item>https://archium.ateneo.edu/un-sdg-icons/1012/thumbnail.jpg</item>
        <item>https://archium.ateneo.edu/un-sdg-icons/1013/thumbnail.jpg</item>
        <item>https://archium.ateneo.edu/un-sdg-icons/1014/thumbnail.jpg</item>
        <item>https://archium.ateneo.edu/un-sdg-icons/1015/thumbnail.jpg</item>
        <item>https://archium.ateneo.edu/un-sdg-icons/1016/thumbnail.jpg</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>